<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Gekaku Blog</title>
        <link>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog</link>
        <description>Gekaku Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plans for This Year]]></title>
            <link>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/plans-for-this-year</link>
            <guid>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/plans-for-this-year</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This year I'm gonna keep it simple.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This year I'm gonna keep it simple.</p>
<p>No flashy gimmicks or out-of-this-world ideas. I need to focus on a few things. Here they are:</p>
<ol>
<li class="">Sprinting</li>
<li class="">Melee</li>
</ol>
<p>Nothing too crazy, just my top 2 goals in life. I won't be ignoring my other 2 goals (Dual Hearts and Trombone), I just feel like it's important to remain focused on a few things to avoid being overwhelmed.</p>
<p>For sprinting, I want to be able to run under 50 seconds in the 400m dash. I won't be focusing on any other race because I feel I perform better over longer distances. My ability to hold form and maintain speed is better than my ability to accelerate.</p>
<p>For Melee, I want to win a tournament. I'm planning on going to many tournaments around the country this year, and not just majors. I want to travel to the locals of different states, and get a lot of practice in with the people there.</p>
<p>When I feel I have a bit more time, I'll finish my Dual Hearts review series and show the world what I've discovered about Dual Hearts. I'll also practice my Trombone, specifically working on Flight of The Bumblebee. I won't stress too much on these 2 goals this year.</p>
<p>I'm a competitor at heart, so the first 2 goals are a must. Especially sprinting. I'm turning 28 this year, and I may only have about 6-7 years left in my physical prime. I really want to see how fast I can get.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dealing With Expectations]]></title>
            <link>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/dealing-with-expectations</link>
            <guid>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/dealing-with-expectations</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The more I look back on my August 14th post, the more it feels like I need to elaborate more on what I'm saying. Especially that last paragraph, which seemed pretty jarring. This blog is a place where I get personal and hold no punches, so expect to see more of that as time goes on.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The more I look back on my August 14th post, the more it feels like I need to elaborate more on what I'm saying. Especially that last paragraph, which seemed pretty jarring. This blog is a place where I get personal and hold no punches, so expect to see more of that as time goes on.</p>
<p>A few days ago my cousin was ran over by multiple cars and killed. It was a shock to me and many others, including my dad. He talked to me about how sad it was that he did not reach his full potential. He used my cousin's death as an example of what I would become if I didn't start taking action and get a stable income.</p>
<p>My late cousin was out on the streets. As far as I know, he was just walking around as a homeless man. He had a history of drug use. My dad believes he might have been on drugs during the time of the accident. I didn't know much about his personal life because I hadn't seen him in about 3-4 years.</p>
<p>My dad gives me lectures about how I need to stop surviving and start thriving. I, however, don't see the way I'm living as surviving or thriving. I would call it adapting. I've talked about my situation in prior posts, but I'll go in a bit more detail.</p>
<p>In mid October of this year, I made the trip back home to Houston. I shipped my car back, and am in the process to get it fixed so I can get back to traveling. Including that, my other main goals are balding Gamecube controller buttons to sell at the next Genesis, resting to get back to sprint training, and training my Melee Pikachu.</p>
<p>These are things my dad is fine with. What he's not fine with is that I do not have a stable income. I left my jobs at Wendy's and Home Depot when I left Albuquerque. That's right, I'm unemployed. And when people are unemployed in this country they are seen as lazy and entitled. "Why can't they find a job and work like the rest of us?" is what I assume pops up in many employed people's heads when they see someone like me.</p>
<p>My dad tells me he doesn't want me to have the fate of the many male members of my family. I have a transgender older sister who is living a similar life as what my cousin was living through. Right now, she is living on the streets of downtown Houston. I saw her this week for the first time in a few years when me and my dad drove around downtown looking for her. "When you see him walking, you'll know it's him because no one walks like him". When my dad saw her walking down the street with a fast, flamboyant gait, my dad knew immediately it was her.</p>
<p>We took her to the nearby Jack in the Box, a place she frequents. A worker there told me she comes by late at night, and he feeds her. My dad orders her some food and leaves to buy her some cigarettes. As we sit beside each other at a table, I try to talk to her a bit.</p>
<p>She's very jittery. Almost two times as jittery as when I saw her a few years ago. She responds to everything I say with a fast "yeah", "yup", or "mhm". She stands up and sits back down immediately from time to time. She moves her arms and hands in random patterns. She bangs her head against the back of the seat at times. It was all very unnerving.</p>
<p>The most haunting part of me trying to talk to her was when she looked me in the eyes. She did it before, but they were only fleeting glances. There was one time where she stared at me for a solid 5 seconds. During those 5 seconds I tried to find her old self within her eyes. I wanted to see a small glint of hope that she was still in there, that the drugs didn't take her completely. Unfortunately, all I saw was nothingness. It felt as if those wide, blood shot eyes had nothing beyond them.</p>
<p>My dad tells me he wishes that I don't become like my sister. He believes we are put on this earth to grow. Not just physically, but spiritually. He also tells me he doesn't want to live life worrying about my well-being. But why should I care what he thinks about me? I wasn't brought into this world by choice. Why should I have to live my life to quell his worries? I have the free will to do what I want, just like he has the free will to worry.</p>
<p>He brought my sister into this world, and she hasn't lived up to his expectations. So what? She didn't live up to my expectations either. Do you think I want my sister to be living the way she is? Although I don't like the way she's living, it was her choice. I won't be living my life in hopes that my dad will be proud of me. Whatever I do will be of my own volition, and I won't be looking to others for approval.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Life Has Been Going These Past Few Years]]></title>
            <link>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/how-life-has-been-going-these-past-few-years</link>
            <guid>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/how-life-has-been-going-these-past-few-years</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An X/Twitter I made on December 31, 2022 about how long the year has felt because of the challenges I have faced.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" alt="An X/Twitter I made on December 31, 2022 about how long the year has felt because of the challenges I have faced." src="https://blog.gekaku.com/assets/images/XSS-1-255247b944900704cba9b78bc414e774.png" width="670" height="237" class="img_ev3q"></p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" alt="Another X/Twitter post I made on the same day talking about how my goal was now to reach 10k subscribers on YouTube now that I have reached 1k subscribers" src="https://blog.gekaku.com/assets/images/XSS-2-04d96be47ed059abdd42b35934e65e71.png" width="736" height="587" class="img_ev3q"></p>
<p>This was a post I made about 3 years ago. 2022 was a great year for me. I traveled to a lot of tournaments, and got to meet so many people; many of which I wouldn't recognize if I meet again so don't be mad at me please (I can't remember all these got dang faces!).</p>
<p>Anyway, this X/Twitter post I made was of me reflecting on all the traveling, filming, and editing I did the entire year. I was proud of myself for reaching 1,000 subscribers. I never thought I could reach so many people. It gave me hope for the future, and I was so excited to continue this journey.</p>
<p>Then 2023 hit.</p>
<p>This was the worst year of my life.</p>
<p>My Wells Fargo remote job fired me, so I had to stop traveling to work at U-Haul. I had quit my job at U-Haul in 2021 and moved to Albuquerque when I landed the remote job. It felt like I was back at square one.</p>
<p>The remote job was fining me $10,000 because I had breached their contract to stay in Houston. They were ending remote work, but I had no idea I wasn't allowed to move. There are Wells Fargo locations everywhere, so I thought I could just work at any location.</p>
<p>In addition to U-Haul, I also decided to work at Whataburger to make more money to pay for the fine.</p>
<p>All of these things hit me so hard. I had no idea what to do. I felt like I had failed. I was just at the top of the world, traveling to several different states and even Canada. Now I'm stuck in a small fast food kitchen taking orders.</p>
<p>After a few months working at Whataburger, I decided to quit. My mental health was deteriorating, and it was taking everything in me not to just up and leave while on the shift. They mainly had me at the window taking orders or handing the food out. It was tearing me up inside having to stand in one spot without any freedom of movement.</p>
<p>After about 7-8 months working at U-Haul, I decided to drive back to Houston for a break. I was only planning to be there for about a month. Unfortunately, my car was having issues, and would not be able to handle the long drive back to Albuquerque. I needed to make some money to fix the car before I could make my trip back. I called my boss at the U-Haul location in Albuquerque and asked him to transfer me to my old location in Houston.</p>
<p>This was an amazing experience. Initially, I felt like an utter failure having to go back to the job I had left when I got my remote job opportunity with Wells Fargo. I was back in the same place I was when I started. It felt embarrassing seeing the coworkers I had told I was leaving for a better job just about a year ago. I thought I was back at square one.</p>
<p>However, this feeling within me did not remain that way. My coworkers were so kind and understanding. They did not look down or belittle me, they welcomed me and appreciated my presence. I had a lot of fun hanging out with them. It never felt like I was working when I was around them. My mental health was improving through an unexpected source.</p>
<p>Before I left back to Albuquerque, me and my coworkers had a going away party at an Anime bar. I'm so glad I got the chance to go back to my old job. It not only humbled me, but changed the way I viewed success. I no longer want to work in a office job or even a salaried job. I feel that true success is when you are able to do what you want without fear of failure. The happiness I felt going back to the U-Haul in Houston showed me that as long as I'm around people who uplift and make me happy, I don't care how much money I'm making.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why I Deleted My Social Media]]></title>
            <link>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/why-i-deleted-my-social-media</link>
            <guid>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/why-i-deleted-my-social-media</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[I deleted my social media accounts because they are getting in the way of me accomplishing my goals. They have become distractions to my mission.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I deleted my social media accounts because they are getting in the way of me accomplishing my goals. They have become distractions to my mission.</p>
<p>My main goal is to become the fastest human being of all time. Although I have other ambitions, they are not as important as this one. I have decided to do whatever it takes to accomplish this goal. That includes removing the things in my life that have become hindrances.</p>
<p>I actually have 4 main goals, but sprinting is the one I will be spending the most time on. Here they are in order of least to most important:</p>
<ol>
<li class="">Sprinting</li>
<li class="">Melee</li>
<li class="">Dual Hearts</li>
<li class="">Trombone</li>
</ol>
<p>No matter how much I look at this list, I can’t find any way to compromise and fit other things in. I’m barely gonna have enough time as it is to work on these things. After a lot of time thinking and reflecting, I decided to throw away several other goals and just focus on these ones.</p>
<p>I will still be making content (Heck, I’m doing it right now), but I will only be posting content on a few websites and YouTube.</p>
<p>There’s one last thing I want to say. I’ve made some promises to people involving creating videos or playing a certain video game. I want to apologize for not completing those promises. I can no longer live a life where I am not focusing on myself. It has worn me down far too long trying to satisfy others. I am a truly selfish person at heart, and I can not lie to myself any longer. Any action I make from now on will be of my own volition.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[My Time In Taos]]></title>
            <link>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/my-time-in-taos</link>
            <guid>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/my-time-in-taos</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[After failing to generate much profit from the Rectangle Corner booth we had at Super Nova 2024, I decided to get a few jobs to get more money for the business. I went on Indeed and saw a job as a crew member for the Rocky Mountain Youth Corps. I applied and got a quick response back, which is what I was looking for. I had no interest in waiting it out to see if there were better job offers. I just wanted to make some money and obtain a new experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After failing to generate much profit from the Rectangle Corner booth we had at Super Nova 2024, I decided to get a few jobs to get more money for the business. I went on Indeed and saw a job as a crew member for the Rocky Mountain Youth Corps. I applied and got a quick response back, which is what I was looking for. I had no interest in waiting it out to see if there were better job offers. I just wanted to make some money and obtain a new experience.</p>
<p>After landing the job, I applied around and got another job at Wendy’s. I was working about 60 hours a week at these two jobs. The Youth Corps job was 8 days on and 6 days off. I would work at Wendy’s on the days off.</p>
<div class="theme-tabs-container tabs-container tabList__CuJ"><ul role="tablist" aria-orientation="horizontal" class="tabs"><li role="tab" tabindex="0" aria-selected="true" class="tabs__item tabItem_LNqP tabs__item--active">Youth Corps</li><li role="tab" tabindex="-1" aria-selected="false" class="tabs__item tabItem_LNqP">Wendy's</li><li role="tab" tabindex="-1" aria-selected="false" class="tabs__item tabItem_LNqP">UPS</li><li role="tab" tabindex="-1" aria-selected="false" class="tabs__item tabItem_LNqP">Conclusion</li></ul><div class="margin-top--md"><div role="tabpanel" class="tabItem_Ymn6"><iframe width="646" height="363" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3tXFqQgejw8" title="What I Got Goin' On" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" style="display:block;margin-bottom:1.5rem"></iframe><p>I had an amazing time at the Youth Corps. It was my first time camping outside. I can’t believe how fulfilling it is to set up a tent, make a campfire, and just hang out around it. It taught me that there is way more fun to be had outside than being cooped up inside all of the time.</p></div><div role="tabpanel" class="tabItem_Ymn6" hidden=""><p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" alt="A picture of me in the bathroom of Wendy&amp;#39;s. I have my Wendy&amp;#39;s uniform on, and I have a newly shaven head" src="https://blog.gekaku.com/assets/images/wendys-1-52a34635dfe50ce23d4cf85df5b6d96b.jpg" width="3968" height="2232" class="img_ev3q"></p><p>My time at Wendy’s was surprising. I didn’t expect to have a good experience because of how boring and tedious my last fast food job at Whataburger was. It turned out to be a slightly more impactful experience than the Youth Corps, believe it or not. I made so many friends, and even got to hang out at one of my coworker’s houses for Christmas. Not to mention the free food! I’m actually planning on going back to Taos next year, and the main reason for that is because of the people I befriended at this one rundown Wendy’s in the small town of Taos.</p></div><div role="tabpanel" class="tabItem_Ymn6" hidden=""><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5d6QYS3Vf94?si=WTnPnI7fCOV_g9kq" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin"></iframe><p>After the season at the Youth Corps was over, I decided to stay for a few more months. While I was going to pick up some mail, a UPS worker told me they were hiring, so I decided to apply. Luckily, I was hired immediately, because I wasn’t keen on waiting for another job. I was still in that money making mode. I was a pre-loader, which is a person who loads the trucks with packages before the UPS drivers get there to begin their routes. This job was probably the 2nd physically hardest job I’ve had (The Youth Corps takes the #1 spot because of how hard it is to go several miles uphill and downhill daily) because of how cold it was in the morning. It was also difficult waking up at 4am and walking into the sheer cold. It was slightly easier for me because I would sleep in my car right outside of the facility.</p></div><div role="tabpanel" class="tabItem_Ymn6" hidden=""><p>Overall, I would say that my time in Taos was incredible. I can’t believe I had the courage to go and visit the unknown while sleeping in my car, which is another unknown. I had no idea if it would work, but I made it work. I’m glad I did this because it showed me what’s truly important to me; and that’s enjoying life and experiencing new things. And I don’t need to live in a house or apartment to do that.</p></div></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Jobs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[My Car]]></title>
            <link>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/My-Car</link>
            <guid>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/My-Car</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This is my car]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is my car</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" alt="My car with a new roof rack for extra storage during travels." src="https://blog.gekaku.com/assets/images/car-dccaec4e01af786d695bf223e90027b9.jpg" width="4032" height="2268" class="img_ev3q"></p>
<p>I have spent the past few months soft modifying the vehicle. I recently added a roof rack to the top to help with space and a few other things for when I start traveling.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" alt="A netting around my car door" src="https://blog.gekaku.com/assets/images/outside-car-9d4962734b8a7b7e5a0cdc31498e17c6.jpg" width="4032" height="2268" class="img_ev3q"></p>
<p>This wrap around the window is a life saver when it’s hot outside
I use these net-like wraps around my vehicle to help with the heat. Without these, I wouldn’t be able to sleep in the car. Before I bought these, I was sweating like a dog!</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" alt="A view of the car&amp;#39;s inside" src="https://blog.gekaku.com/assets/images/car-within-from-outside-df2285c1f4ef5d0ae7ae1eeba2685282.jpg" width="4032" height="2268" class="img_ev3q"></p>
<p>This is the inside of the vehicle. If you look closely at the two rear doors, you can see that I took off the door panels off. My battery died, so I have to manually open and close the windows when I leave for work. It actually isn’t that annoying. I might leave it off because it gives me slightly more space.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" alt="A netting around my car door" src="https://blog.gekaku.com/assets/images/within-car-ea7e81159a428adbdfe8c08797fc93b3.jpg" width="4032" height="2268" class="img_ev3q"></p>
<p>This is a closer look inside of the car. It’s a bit messy, but I’m getting better at organizing as time goes on.</p>
<p>Overall, I think this is an improved version of the setup I had when I was in Taos. I just realized I never talked about the Taos trip. The trip is very important because it inspired me to do what I’m planning on doing. I’ll talk about that in the next post.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Car</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Blog Post]]></title>
            <link>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/first-blog-post</link>
            <guid>https://blog.gekaku.com/blog/first-blog-post</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This is my first day making a website from scratch. Gotta start somewhere. Ok, so what should I put here? How about a video of me working?]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is my first day making a website from scratch. Gotta start somewhere. Ok, so what should I put here? How about a video of me working?</p>
<iframe width="646" height="363" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sWUFkmFFzTg" title="Workin' at Home Depot" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="" style="display:block;margin-bottom:1.5rem"></iframe>
<p>This is me working at Home Depot. I am an overnight stocker. This is a full time job. I also work at Wendy’s for the other 2 days out of the week.</p>
<p>I’ve been trying to save up money to start traveling to these video game tournaments again. I’ve moved out of the place I was at, and am sleeping in my car right now to save up money.</p>
<p>This is also practice for when I am traveling. To save money, I’ll be sleeping in my car. I’ll explain more in the next diary entry.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>Jobs</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>